Finding Aid for Medical-Surgical Nursing Area (University of Michigan) records, 1960-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty and Staff
  - Josephine Sana Files 1975-1982
    - Student Survey Results 1975-1977 (Box 17)
    - Unification 1979-1980 (Box 17)